A witch! A witch!
A witch! We found a witch!
We've got a witch!
A witch! A witch!
Whoa there!
We have found a witch.
Maywe burn her?
- How do you know she is a witch?
- She looks like one.
Bring her forward.
I'm not a witch!
But you are dressed as one.
- They dressed me like this.
- No, we didn't.
And this isn't my nose.
It's a false one.
Whoa there!
- Well?
- We did do the nose.
- The nose?
- And the hat. But she is a witch!
- Did you dress her up like this?
- No, no!
Yes. A bit.
She has got a wart.
What makes you think
she's a witch?
She turned me into a newt!
A newt?
I got better.
Burn her anyway!
Quiet! Quiet!
There are ways of telling
whether she is a witch.
- Are there? What are they? Tell us.
- Do they hurt?
Tell me, what do you do with witches?
Burn them!
And what do you burn,
apart from witches?
- More witches!
- Wood!
So why do witches burn?
- 'Cause they're made of wood?
- Good!
- How do we tell if she is made ofwood?
- Build a bridge out ofher.
But can you not also make bridges
out of stone?
Oh, yeah.
Does wood sink in water?
- No, it floats.
- Throw her into the pond!
What also floats in water?
- Bread.
- Apples.
- Very small rocks.
- Cider! Great gravy.
- Cherries. Mud.
- Churches.
- Lead.
- A duck!
Exactly.
So, logically--
If she weighs the same as a duck...
she's made of wood.
And therefore?
A witch!
- A duck! A duck!
- Here's a duck.
We shall use my largest scales.
Burn the witch!
Remove the supports!
A witch!
It's a fair cop.
Whoa there!
Who are you, who are so wise
in the ways of science?
I am Arthur, king of the Britons.
My Liege!
Good Sir Knight, will you come with me
to Camelot...
and join us at the Round Table?
My Liege, I would be honored!
- What is your name?
- Bedevere, my Liege.
Then I dub you Sir Bedevere...
Knight of the Round Table.
The wise Sir Bedevere was the first
to join King Arthur's knights.
But other illustrious names
were soon to follow.
"Sir Lancelot the Brave.
Sir Galahad the Pure.
And Sir Robin the
Not-Quite-So-Brave-As Sir Lancelot...
who had nearly fought
the Dragon of Angnor...
who nearly stoodup to
the Chicken of Bristol...
and wet himself at
the Battle of Badon Hill.
And the aptly named,
Sir Not-Appearing-In-This-Film.
Together they formed a band
whose names and deeds...
were retold throughout the centuries. "
The Knights of the Round Table.
And that, my Liege, is how we know
the Earth to be banana-shaped.